Guide to the John McCarthy Papers SC0524
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Original Accession, Accession ARCH-1995-247
  - Wilks, Yorick, 1971-1976, (articles, correspondence, proposals, program listing) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Winograd, Terry, 1972-1978, (drafts of articles, articles) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Wood, Lowell, 1972-1977, (letter, article) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Wilkins, David, 1973-1978, (articles, correspondence, drafts of articles, program listings) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Weyhraugh, Richard, 1973-1981, (article, lecture notes, draft of article, program listings) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Wickelgren, Wayne, 1969-1984, (letter, curriculum vitae, article, reprints) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - US Labor Party, 1976-1978, (constitution, journals) (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Wadler, Phil, l977, (article) (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Thomas, Arthur, 1971-1978, (correspondence, memo, draft of manuscript chapters, draft of article, proposals, article) (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Tappel, Steve, 1981, (problem statement) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Uniform, 1981, (article) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Tang, Chih-Sung, 1974-1982, (reprint, articles, correspondence) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Suppes, Patrick, 1970-1979, (reprints, article, memo) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Sussman, Gerald, 1972, (article, report) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Suzuki, Norihisa, 1973-1976, (articles, program listing) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Takasu, Satoru, 1976-1979, (article, correspondence) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Stoyan, Herbert, 1976-1982, (curriculum vitae, correspondence, drafts of articles) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Scott, Dana, 1970, (articles, drafts of articles) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Schwartz, Jack, 1975-1976, (memo, correspondence, article, reprints, report) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Pnueli, Amir, 1969-1976, (correspondence, curriculum vitae, articles, reprints) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Prolog, 1974-1981, (articles) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Reiter, Raymond, 1971-1981, (correspondence, reprints, articles, technical reports) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Py lyshyn, Zenon, 1973-1979, (reprints, articles, draft of article) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - AI Memo List, 1963-1984 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Proposal, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Placement of Engineering Graduates, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Reports, articles - Stanford, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Reports, articles - non-Stanford (Box 9)
  - Reports, articles - non-Stanford (MIT), 1973-1980 (Box 10)
  - A. B. Dick Copier, 1970, (instructions) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Ampex Memory Level Converters, 1971, (notes, letter, list) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 128K Ampex Interface, 1972, (notes) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Centronics Printer, (manual, notes, brochure) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - IBM 2314, 1970, (manual) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Cache and Schottky Info, 1969-1971, (product specifications, reports, brochures, article, price list) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Acoustic Coupler (Tymshare) and TTY EIA Interface Adapter, 1966-1968, (diagrams, blueprints,brochure) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Microswitch, 1965-1971, (diagrams, blueprints, correspondence, manual, list) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - E. R. L. Stock Room, 1964, (components lists) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Modems, 1970, (product specifications, brochures, article) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Video Synthesizer (ARDS), 1970, (diagrams) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - IMLAC Corp., 1970, (correspondence, notes, diagrams, manuals) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - IMLAC Displays, 1969-1983, (manuals, lists, reprints, blueprints, correspondence) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Videograph Display Copier, 1971, (manuals) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - LRL Reports and Misc. - Lawrence Radiation Labs, 1957-1963, (blueprints, reports) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Operating notes, memos, program listing, reprints, 1964-1979 (Box 11)
  - LISP manuals (Box 11)
  - Rancho Arm, 1966-1968, (correspondence, subcontract) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - III Eye, 1966-1970, (correspondence, subcontract and amendment) (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - ARDS - Advanced Remote Display Station, 1968-1970, (price list, reports, manuals, brochures) (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Manuals, IMLAC Corp. (Box 11)
  - DEC - Digital Equipment Corp., 1965-1971, (correspondence, subcontract, memos, product specifications0 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - 3 technical reports, non-Stanford, 1962-1970 (Box 11)
  - Manuals, catalogs, journals, miscellaneous information on Robert Poor, 1964-1979 (Box 12)
  - E. E. Stores - Electrical Engineering Stores, 1968-1969, (lists, forms, memos) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Speech Notes, 1969, (articles) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Catalog, brochures, proposals, diagrams, memos, correspondence, reports, 1965-1970 (Box 13)
  - Proposals, manual, 1967-1970 (Box 13)
  - Librascope Log Notes, 1963-1971, (program listing, notes, correspondence, diagrams, log, lists, blueprints) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Manual, 1970 (Box 13)
  - Proposal, 1970 (Box 13)
  - Core RFP - Core Request For Proposal, 1967, (specifications, proposals) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - III Display Proposal - Information International Inc. Display Proposal, 1966-1968, (proposal, notes, correspondence, character set, specifications) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Straza Displays for PDP-6, 1964-1966, (correspondence, proposals, memos, request for proposal, notes, specifications, blueprints - Straza and other companies) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Operating Notes 3-4, 1967-1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Operating Notes 5-7, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Operating Note 8, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Operating Note 9, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Operating Notes 10-12, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Operating Notes 13-20, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Operating Notes 21-23, 1967-1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Operating Notes 24-26, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Operating Note 27, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Operating Note 28.3, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Operating Note 28.4, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Operating Note 28.6 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Operating Note 28.7 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Operating Notes 29-31, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Operating Note 32, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Operating Notes 33-35, 1965-1968 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Operating Note 35.1, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Operating Notes 36-37, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Operating Notes 38-42, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Operating Notes 43-45, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Operating Notes 46-47, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Operating Note 48, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Operating Notes 49-50, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Operating Note 51, 1969-1973 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Operating Notes 52-53, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Operating Note 54 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Operating Note 54, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Operating Note 54.3, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Operating Note 54.4, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Operating Note 55, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Operating Note 55, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Operating Note 55, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Operating Note 55.3, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Stanford Time-Sharing Memos, 1963-1965 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Operating Note 57.1, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Operating Notes 58-59, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Operating Note 60, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Operating Note 63, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Memo AI-66, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Operating Note 71, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Operating Note 71, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Operating Note 73, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Reports, memos AIM - Stanford, 1972-1979 (Box 15)
  - Reports, articles, 1975-1979 (Box 15)
  - Articles, book, 1963-1966 (Box 15)
  - Manuals, program listings, articles, reports, 1960-1964 (Box 15)
  - Reports - non-Stanford, 1972-1985, 1960-1965 (Box 16)
  - Journals, 1963-1964, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Memo, manuals, notebook, reports, articles, 1955-1965 (Box 17)
  - Reports - SRI, 1969-1979 (Box 17)
  - Articles, list, 1956-1979 (Box 17)
  - Reprints, 1953-1961 (Box 18)
  - Articles, course description, 1981-1982 (Box 18)
  - aisb - artificial intelligence and simulation of behavior - Quarterly, 1978-1983 (Box 18)
  - MIT Artificial Intelligence Memos, 1958-1962 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - MIT Artificial Intelligence Memos, Feb-Apr 1963 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - MIT Artificial Intelligence Memos, May-Jul 1963 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - MIT Artificial Intelligence Memos, Oct-Dec 1963 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - MIT Artificial Intelligence Memos, Jan-Sep 1964 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Reports - MIT, 1968-1981 (Box 18)
  - Brochures, correspondence, proposals, 1965-1968 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Brochures, proposals, 1966-1974 (Box 18)
  - Two binders of diagrams - Digital Equipment Corp., 1961-1974 (Box 18)
  - Binder of diagrams - Digital Equipment Corp., 1964-1967 (Box 19)
  - Binder of diagrams - Digital Equipment Corp., 1961-1967 (Box 19)
  - DEC - Digital Equipment Corp. and BBN - Bolt, Beranek and Newman Corp. ECOs - Engineering Change Orders to PDP-10, 1969-1971 (stairclimber - blueprints, foldered ECOs) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - IBM 2314-A2, 1967-1969, (manuals) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - IBM 3330, 1971, (manual) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - DSKTST, 1966-1971, (program listings, articles) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Ampex Interface, 1971, (notes, diagrams, article) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - TTY Multiplexer, 1971-1972, (blueprint, notes, diagrams) (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - System Power Consumption, (notes) (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Instructional TV, 1971-1972, (notes, class schedule) (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Memory Bus Cables, Stanford Applied Engineering, 1965-1971, (notes, diagrams, blueprints, correspondence) (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Order forms (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Data Disc Keyboard and Teletype Information, 1967-1972 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Dvorak Keyboard, 1943, 1971-1977, (articles) (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Central Data, 1980, (brochure, reprints) (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Electronic Solutions, 1980, (brochure, price list) (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Spectronics, 1979-1980, (brochure, list, reprint) (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - DCA - Digital Communications Associates, Inc., 1980, (letter, brochure) (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - UDS - Universal Data Systems, 1976-1980, (manual, brochures) (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Power-One, 1976-1981, (brochures) (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Manufacturers Representatives - line cards, 1980, (brochures) (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Maps, schedules, time tables, etc., (map) (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Clement Labs, 1980, (letter) (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Motorola Displays, 1978-1979, (brochure) (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Nationwide Electronic Systems, Inc., 1980, (letter, brochure) (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Airpax, 1978-1980, (letter, brochures) (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Douglas Randall, (brochures) (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Xsis Electronics, (brochure) (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Computrol Corp., 1980, (brochure) (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Ann Arbor Terminals, Inc., 1980, (letter, brochure) (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Motorola, Discrete Semiconductor Div., 1976, (brochures) (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Racal-Vadic, 1980, (brochure) (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Micom, 1980, (catalog) (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - IDS - International Data Sciences, Inc., 1980, (price list) (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Paradyne, (brochure, price list) (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Moxon, 1980, (brochure) (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - TV Antenna Information, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Vector Electronic Co., (brochure page) (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - AMD - Advanced Micro Devices Inc., 1976-1979, (brochures) (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Synertek, Inc., 1978-1979, (specifications, brochure) (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Wire Wrap, 1969-1980, (brochures, article) (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Pro-Log, 1979-1980, (newsletter, reprint, brochures) (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Binder of Digital Equipment Corp -DEC diagrams, 1964-1967 (Box 20)
  - DEC Manual, 1972 (Box 20)
  - Two binders of DEC diagrams, 1961-1965 (Box 20)
  - DEC Diagrams, loose, 1964-1971 (Box 20)
  - Binder of lists (Box 20)
  - Binder of brochures (Box 20)
  - Binder of DEC diagrams, 1963-1965 (Box 20)
  - Binder of DEC diagrams, 1959-1964 (Box 20)
  - DEC Manuals, 1964, 1967 (Box 20)
  - Russian Computer Connection - Russ. Comp. Con., 1985, (report - Stanford) (Box 20)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1959-1961, 1983-1986, (reports - non-Stanford) (Box 20)
  - Russian Computer Connection - Russ. Comp. Con., 1962-1977, (reprints, newspaper, notes, correspondence) (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1958-1985, (reprints, magazines) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., (photographs) (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1964, (envelopes, travel brochures, article) (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1966, (Rand documents) (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1966-1974, (correspondence, articles) (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1975, (Pacific Legal Foundation) (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1966-1972, (correspondence) (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1966, (article, miscellaneous) (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1966, (notes - Russian and English) (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1965-1975, (correspondence) (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1965-1971, (correspondence, articles) (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1965-1966, (correspondence, conference program) (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1964-1965, (agreement, US and USSR, scientific exchanges) (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1960-1966, (correspondence, list, program listing) (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1970, (map reprints, notes, photographs) (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1966-1970, (brochures, notes, articles, correspondence) (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1962-1966, (correspondence, reprints, article) (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1965-1972, (photographs, correspondence, articles) (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1971, 1973, (Rand documents) (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1972, (Rand documents) (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1972-1978, (misc. travel info., photograph with letter) (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1967, (Tata Institute of Fundamental Research, Bombay - articles) (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1969, (Tata Institute of Fundamental Research, Bombay - articles) (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1965, (reprint, articles) (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1966, 1970, (Computer chess - clippings) (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1967, (Computer chess - lists, program listing, notes) (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., (Russian article, notes) (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1967-1973, (Computer chess - notes, articles, correspondence) (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1963-1971, (Computer chess - program listing, lists, articles, correspondence) (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1978, (article, correspondence) (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1973, (Manfred Sakel Institute - correspondence, articles) (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1971, (Manfred Sakel Institute - correspondence, articles, lists) (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Russ. Comp. Con., 1970, (Manfred Sakel Institute - correspondence, articles, lists) (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Brochures (Box 22)
  - 1965, (student papers) (Box 22)
  - 1955-1963, (memo, LISP manual) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 1948-1956, (reprints, articles) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - 1931-1958, (reprints, articles) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - 1957, (report, article, handbook) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - 1946-1956, (reprints) (Box 22)
  - Three binders, (lecture notes, reports) (Box 22)
  - 1956-1957, (articles) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Four binders, 1956, (class-related notes) (Box 22)
  - Binder, 1956, (proposal) (Box 22)
  - 1958-1960, (memos, reprints) (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - 1954-1957, (articles, proposal, memo) (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - 1955, (articles, report) (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Mathematics and Social Sciences, 1955, (binder) (Box 22)
  - 1951-1958, (articles) (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - 1922-1960, (reprints) (Box 22)
  - Journals, 1951, 1962 (Box 23)
  - Reports - non-Stanford, 1949-1959 (Box 23)
  - Reports - non-Stanford, 1966-1979 (Box 23)
  - 1969, (article) (Box 24)
  - Reports - non-Stanford, 1966-1977 (Box 24)
  - 1965-1979, (reports, articles, reprints, dissertation) (Box 24)
  - 1979, (transparencies, article) (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Transparencies (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Slides for Circumscription, (transparencies) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Circumscription, 1983-1984, (articles, transparencies) (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Circumscription Misc. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Transparencies (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Conference on Art of Computer Programming, Nov 1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Conference on Art of Computer Programming, Nov 1978, (program listing) (Box 25)
  - Conference on Art of Computer Programming, Nov 1978, (articles, reprint, transparencies, notes) (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Conference on Art of Computer Programming, Nov 1978, Ershov correspondence (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Conference on Art of Computer Programming, Nov 1978, (articles, listing) (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Memos, articles, reprints, 1950-1956, journal, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - 1956-1970, (articles) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Binder, (memos) (Box 25)
  - Reports - Stanford, 1956-1961 (Box 25)
  - Binder, 1960, (notes) (Box 25)
  - 1958, (articles) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - 1956-1959, (articles) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Binder, 1956, (memos) (Box 25)
  - Reports - non-Stanford, 1954-1984 (Box 25)
  - Pony Cash Flow, 1977-1979 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Chron Binder 1, Aug 1979-Jan 1978 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Chron Binder 2, Jul 1978-Dec 1978 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Purchase Req., Chron, 1970-1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Binder, Office Manual - Secretary, Part 2 (Box 26)
  - Capitol Equipment Binder, [1 of 3] (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Capitol Equipment Binder, [2 of 3] (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Capitol Equipment Binder, [3 of 3] (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Blanket Orders Binder, A-D (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Blanket Orders Binder, E-F (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Blanket Orders Binder, G-L (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Blanket Orders Binder, M-O (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Blanket Orders Binder, P-S (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Blanket Orders Binder, T-V (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Blanket Orders Binder, W-Z (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Blanket Orders Binder, Xerox Rental (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Orders (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Purchase Requisitions Binder (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Purchase Requisitions Binder, Feb 1984-Jan 1981, [1 of 4] (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Purchase Requisitions Binder, 1980, [2 of 4] (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Purchase Requisitions Binder, 1979, [3 of 4] (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Purchase Requisitions Binder, 1979-1978, [4 of 4] (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Completed Purchase Requisitions Binder, 1978-1979, [1 of 5] (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Completed Purchase Requisitions Binder, 1978-1979, [2 of 5] (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Completed Purchase Requisitions Binder, 1978-1979, [3 of 5] (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Completed Purchase Requisitions Binder, 1978-1979, [4 of 5] (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Completed Purchase Requisitions Binder, 1978-1979, [5 of 5] (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Completed Purchase Requisitions Binder 1, 1979-1980, [1 of 4] (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Completed Purchase Requisitions Binder 1, 1979-1980, [2 of 4] (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Completed Purchase Requisitions Binder 1, 1979-1980, [3 of 4] (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Completed Purchase Requisitions Binder 1, 1979-1980, [4 of 4] (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Completed Purchase Requisitions Binder 2, 1979-1980, [1 of 5] (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Completed Purchase Requisitions Binder 2, 1979-1980, [2 of 5] (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Completed Purchase Requisitions Binder 2, 1979-1980, [3 of 5] (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Completed Purchase Requisitions Binder 2, 1979-1980, [4 of 5] (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Completed Purchase Requisitions Binder 2, 1979-1980, [5 of 5] (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - AI (Artificial Intelligence) Project and Misc., 1960's (proposals) (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - AI Project and Misc., 1965-1974 (correspondence, memos) (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - AI Project and Misc., 1965-1966 (correspondence, memos) (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - AI Project and Misc., 1965-1966 (correspondence, memos, proposals) (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - AI Project and Misc., 1964-1968 (correspondence, memos) (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Impact of Military Research on University, 1972 (articles, letter, notes) (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - AI Research, Time-Sharing, Large Memory Computer, 1963-1965 (notes, proposals) (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Exploration of Mars and Misc., 1964-1965 (correspondence, reports, proposals) (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Exploration of Mars/Extraterrestrial Life 1964-1965 (correspondence, reports, bibliography) (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Exploration of Mars/Extraterrestrial Life 1964-1965 (reports, memos) (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Mathematics, 1955-? (notes) (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Mathematics, 1947-1948 (notes) (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Mathematics, (notes) (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - LISP, Public Affairs, 1965-1970 (reprint, list, articles) (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Proposals Evaluated, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Mathematics, Chess, Misc., 1955-1956 (notes) (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Dartmouth Mathematical Project ("On the Mathematical Aspects of the Aggregation Problem in the Leontief Open Model" and "A Generalization of the Von Neumann Model of an Expanding Economy") (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Chess, Misc. (notes) (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - MIT AI Group, Chess, Language (notes) (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Epistemology, Language, Lectures (articles, notes) (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - IFIP (International Federation for Information Processing), 1964 [1 of 2] (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - IFIP, 1964 [2 of 2] (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Misc., ALGOL, Time-Sharing, 1959-1965 (correspondence, articles, newsletter) (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Advice-Taker (print-out, correspondence, article) (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Notes, 1946-1956? [1 of 5] (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Notes, 1946-1956? [2 of 5] (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Notes, 1946-1956? [3 of 5] (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Notes, 1946-1956? [4 of 5] (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Notes, 1946-1956? [5 of 5] (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Computation, 1961 (articles, proposal request) (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Mathematics (notes) (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Space Science Board - Exobiology Study, 1964 (correspondence, reports) [1 of 2] (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Space Science Board - Exobiology Study, 1964 (correspondence, reports) [2 of 2] (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Binder, 1971-1972 (articles) (Box 28)
  - Russian Documents, 1968 1972 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Documents (reprints, contracts, magazine) (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Language, 1958 (notes, articles) [1 of 2] (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Language, 1958 (notes, articles) [2 of 2] (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Multi-Processor Computers, 1965 (notes, articles) (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Language, LISP (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Language, Symbolic Expressions, LISP (articles, notes) [1 of 4] (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Language, Symbolic Expressions, LISP (articles, notes) [2 of 4] (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Language, Symbolic Expressions, LISP (articles, notes) [3 of 4] (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Language, Symbolic Expressions, LISP (articles, notes) [4 of 4] (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Glasnost, 1987-1990 (7 issues) (Box 28)
  - Computer Science Division Technical Reports, 1964-1966 (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961-1964 (Box 28)
  - Student Papers, 1960-1962 (Box 28)
  - Student Papers, 1962-1965 (Box 29)
  - MIT, 1958-1963 (proposal, publications, reports) (Box 29)
  - Miscellaneous, 1959-1960 (reports, brochures) (Box 29)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961-1964 (reports, brochures, publications) (Box 30)
  - Computer Reference Manuals, 1973-1976 (Box 30)
  - LOTS (Stanford Low Overhead Timesharing System) Manuals, 1978 (Box 30)
  - ARPA Contractors Meeting, Dec 1971 (Box 30)
  - ARPA Contractors Meeting, Feb 1971 (Box 31)
  - ARPA Contractors Meeting, Jan 1973 (Box 31)
  - ARPA Contractors Meeting, Feb 1974 (Box 31)
  - Association of Energy Engineers Meeting, "Energy - The New Rules," 1979 (Box 31)